JACOB ALLEN VALDERAMA

WEB DEVELOPER

- **1** 0947-530-7716
- 234 Pulo St., Pinac-pinacan, San Rafael, Bulacan
- jacob-allen-portfolio.vercel.app/

A web developer with expertise in Java, JavaScript, TypeScript, and React frameworks, as well as having a experience in full stack development and user-friendly applications. Demonstrates excellent debugging, problem-solving, and attention to detail. Competent at meeting deadlines and working in a team.

SKILLS

- Skilled in JavaScript and TypeScript for building dynamic web applications, coupled with expertise in HTML/CSS for crafting visually appealing and user-friendly interfaces.
- Experienced in creating powerful server-side applications using Node.js and Java with Spring Boot, complemented by effective database management in MySQL.
- Proficient in developing interactive user interfaces using React and a basic knowledge in using WordPress, Utilizing Firebase for seamless integration of real-time functionalities, and creating efficient REST APIs.

EXPERIENCES

HOOLI SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT SERVICE - OJT

Software Engineer Intern

Feb 2023 - May 2023

Marilao, Bulacan

Roles And Responsibilities:

- A full stack developer in the admin of yokai express project
- Collaboration with other teams and attending weekly scrum meetings
- Use of JIRA ticketing tool for project management
- Learning Java Spring Boot and ReactTS among with other libraries

LJGV PRINTING AND GENERAL MERCHANDISE

IT Support

2019-2020

San Rafael, Bulacan

Roles And Responsibilities:

- Providing and installing of software use for Graphic Designing
- Installing Computer Hardware and Printing Tarpaulins

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Major : Web and Mobile Development Bulacan State University - Bustos Campus

2019-2023

PROJECTS

RESKYUT: MAKE PET ADOPTION FUN AND EASY

Role: Web Developer, Application and Web Testing https://reskyut-landing-page.vercel.app/

YOKAI EXPRESS

Role: Full Stack Developer

https://www.yokaiexpress.com/